Environmental Advocates of New York; Records apap104
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislative Issues, 1930-2004; 1; 58.4 cubic ft.
  - Energy, 1970-1994; 1.4; 7.0 cubic ft.
    - State Energy Plan, Contents of the 1994 Draft PTO (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Hydro-Quebec, Economic Study, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Hydro-Quebec, Economic Study, Draft Appendices, 1992 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Hydro-Quebec, Final Generic Environmental Review, 1993 (Box 7 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
  - Funding, 1972-1995; 1.5; 2.0 cubic ft.
    The subseries Funding contains correspondence, legislative material, news clippings, notes, and testimony related to the Environmental Bond Act, Environmental Protection Fund (EPF), Environmental Trust Fund (ETF), and Capital District Coalition.
    - Bond Act, Others, 1973-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Clean Water, Clean Air Bond Act, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Environmental Bond Act, 1972; 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Environmental Bond Act, 1-800 BOND ACT, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Activists, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Albany, NY, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Brownfields Programs, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Buffalo, NY, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Capital District Coalition, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Clean Fueled Vehicles for New York State, 1998 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Clippings, 1975-1979 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Clippings, Originals, 1983-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Contact List, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Correspondence, Broome County, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Dam Safety and Flood Control, 1997-1998 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Department of Environmental Conservation (DEC), 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Draft Criteria, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Endorsements, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Flyers, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Forest Preserves, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Fulton, NY, 1982; 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Goals and Objectives, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Green Apple Coalition, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Hearing Testimony, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Historic Preservation, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Implementation, Department of Conservation, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Implementation, Environmental Planning Lobby Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Land Acquisitions, 1982-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Legislation, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Legislation, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Media, ca. 1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Miscellaneous, 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Miscellaneous Notes, ca. 1996-1998 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Nassau, NY, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Environmental Bond Act, News Clippings, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Originals, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Press, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Program #130, 1996 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Requests for Transcripts, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Rochester, NY, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Suffolk, NY, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Superfund, Environmental Planning Lobby, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Superfund, Other, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Support for Act, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Syracuse, NY, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Testimony, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Unions, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Wastewater Treatment, 1999 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Environmental Bond Act, Water Quality Improvements, 1997-1998 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Environmental Protection Fund, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Environmental Protection Fund, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Environmental Protection Fund, Handouts, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Environmental Quality Bond Act, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Environmental Quality Bond Act, Governor's Program, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Environmental Quality Bond Act, Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Environmental Quality Bond Act, Summary, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Environmental Trust Fund, Originals, 1991-1992 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Guide to the Bond Act, 1996 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - The Hidden Price Tags, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1972-1995; 1.6; 8.0 cubic ft.
    The Hazardous Waste subseries contains bills, correspondence, case studies, fact sheets, news clippings, reports, and testimony related to storage, superfunds, siting, incineration, Toxic wastes (Asbestos, Dioxin, etc.), and low level radioactive waste. The bulk of the material in this subseries is concerned with low level radioactive waste.
    - Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, 1973-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, Case Studies and News Clippings, 1972-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, Correspondence, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, Petroleum Bulk Storage, 1985-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Bulk Storage of Hazardous Materials, Proposed Legislation and Comments, 1973-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Citizen Participation Plan, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Chlorine Dioxide (Papers Bleaching), 1976; 1988; 1996; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Coalition Support and Membership, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Dioxin Press Release, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Disposal, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Disposal, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - "Disposable Consumer Items: The Overlooked Mercury Pollution Problem", 1981 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Environmental Radiation in New York State, Annual Report, 1982-1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Environmental Radiation in New York State, Annual Report, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Environmental Radiation in New York State, Annual Report, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Environmental Radiation in New York State, Annual Report, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Facilities, Reports, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Facilities, Reports, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Facilities Siting Plan, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Facilities Task Force, Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Facilities Task Force, Siting, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Federal Superfund, 1981-1984 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Federal Superfund, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Hazardous Packing, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Hazardous Packing, Legislation, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Hazardous Packing, Regulations, Exemptions, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Hazardous Substances, Accident Prevention, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Health Monitoring, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1984-1987 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Household Hazards, Fact Sheet, Undated (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Household Toxins, 1986-1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Incineration, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Inactive Hazardous Waste Sites, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Herbicides, Ecological Effects, 1979-1986 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Hazardous Waste Sites, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Incineration and Alternative Disposal Techniques, 1979-1982 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Incineration and Alternative Disposal Techniques, 1983-1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Infectious Waste, Reports, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Land Burials, 1978-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Lead, 1987-1988; 1991-1993 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Legislation, Bills, 1984-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Liability, 1985; 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Love Canal, 1980; 1983-1984; 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Love Canal, 1987; 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Aid to Local Governments, 1985-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Argument States' Rights, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Baseline Health, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Below Regulatory Concern, 1986-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Bibliography, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Blue Mountain Lake Conference, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Candidate Area Report, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Compact, 1955; 1983-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Concern of Churches, New York State, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Contracts for NYLLRW Disposal, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Decommissioning, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, 1978-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Above Ground, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technologies, From Firms, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, General Information, 1982; 1985-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Incineration, 1983-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Land Burial, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Mines, 1987-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Monitoring, Undated (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Salt Storage, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Disposal Technology, Volunteer Sites, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Emergency Access, Nuclearn Information and Resource Service, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Environmental Impact, 1988-1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Essential Goals, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Exclusionary Report, Executive Summary, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Federal Legislation, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Federal Rules and Regulations, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 37)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, General Information, 1979; 1987-1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 38)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Generators and Industry, 1979; 1983-1984; 1989 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 39)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, "Go it Alone", 1988 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 40)
    - Low Level Radioactive, Waste Disposal Facilities, 1982 (Box 2 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 41)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Interim Storage, 1979; 1983-1989; 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Legislation, Proposed Bills, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Legislation, Siting Law, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Liability for Cleanup, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Miscellaneous, 1994-1995 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, New York State Energy Research and Development Authority, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Low Level Radioactive waste, New York State Energy Research and Development Authority Advisory Council, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, New York State Low Level Waste Group, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Notes, 1985-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Nuclear Regulatory Commission, 1979-1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other Legislation, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Arkansas, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, California, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, General, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Illinois, 1985-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Maine, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Massachusetts, 1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Midwest Compact, 1980-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Nebraska, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, New Jersey, 1984 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, North Carolina, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Pennsylvania, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Pennsylvania, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Texas, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Other States, Vermont, 1986-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Past Years, 1983-1986 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Policy, Memorandums, 1983-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Public Information, 1979; 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 29)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Public Information, Sitting Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 30)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Redefinition of Low Level Waste, 1980; 1984-1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 31)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Site Selection Plans, Undated (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 32)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, State Rules and Regulations, 1974; 1986; 1988 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 33)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Study Bill, Law, and Report, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 34)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Study, Law, Bill, and Reports, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 35)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Status Reports, 1988; 1990 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 36)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Storage Study, 1993 (Box 3 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 37)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Testimony, 1980-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, West Valley, 1979-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, West Valley, 1986-1987 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, West Valley Publications, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Low Level Radioactive Waste, Zero Risk Reduction, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - New York State, General Information, 1979-1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - New York State, Hazardous Waste Management, 1978-1983 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - New York State, Hazardous Waste Management, 1984-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - New York State, Regulations, 1981-1983 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - New York State Sites, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Nitrilotriacetic Acid (NTA), 1984 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Oil Spills, News Clippings, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Other States, 1979-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Petroleum, Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCB's), 1975; 1980-1985 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyl (PCB), Fish, Hudson River, 1985-1988 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyl (PCB), Fish, Hudson River, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCB's), Hudson River Reclamation Project, 1976-1981 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Polychlorinated Biphenyls (PCB's), Hudson River Reclamation Project, 1982-1986 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Radioactive Waste Campaign Literature, 1980-1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Radioactive Waste Dump, News Clippings, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - "Radon: Risk, Reality and Reason", 1990 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - Regulations, Comments and Publication List, 1992 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 23)
    - Remediation, Correspondence and Memorandums, 1989-1991 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 24)
    - Remediation, Fact Sheets, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 25)
    - Remediation, Legislation, Bills, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 26)
    - A Primer on Brownfields in New York State, Undated (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 27)
    - New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 28)
    - Remediation, Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - Remediation, Reports, 1994 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)
    - Remediation, Statues, Undated (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 3)
    - Remediation, Testimony, 1984 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 4)
    - Reports, 1982-1988 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 5)
    - Reports, 1989- (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 6)
    - Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 7)
    - Reports, 1991 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 8)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act (RCRA), 1978-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 9)
    - "Revised Draft New York State Hazardous Waste Facility Siting Plan and 21, Environmental Impact Statement", 1989 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 10)
    - Siting, 1984 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 11)
    - Siting, 1985-1986 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 12)
    - Siting, General Information, 1979-1981 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 13)
    - Siting, General Information, 1982-1984 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 14)
    - Siting, New York State Hazardous Waste Facilities, General Environmental Impact Statement (GEIS) Background, 1979 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 15)
    - Siting, New York State Hazardous Waste Facility, General Environmental Impact Statement (GEIS), Testimony, 1981; 1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 16)
    - Siting, New York Short-Term Solution, 1980-1982 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 17)
    - Siting, Part 361 Draft Siting Regulatory Testimony (1/81), 1980-1981 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 18)
    - Small Generators, 1976-1985 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 19)
    - Small Generators, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 20)
    - Source Reduction, 1980-1987 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 21)
    - Silicon Valley Toxics Action, 1994 (Box 5 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 22)
    - State Pollutant Discharge Elimination System (SPDES), 1980-1982 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 1)
    - State Pollutant Discharge Elimination System (SPDES), 1983-1985 (Box 6 (1-Legislative Issues), Folder 2)